- [MAN] KATE, FURTHER BACK.
- [MAN 2] HEY, BRIAN, TAKE THIS
FILTER IN TWO SECONDS.
- [DIRECTOR] LET'S GET A REAL
LOCK-UP UP THERE, PLEASE.
- [MAN 3] GET A PLATE.
- STEVE? STEVE, EXCUSE FOR A
MINUTE.
- [DIRECTOR] GUYS, STOP
WORKING FOR JUST A SECOND.
WE'RE ROLLING, ROLLING.
READY?
- [MAN 4] ROLLING, ROLLING.
- [DIRECTOR] HOUSE LIGHTS!
STAGE!
ACTION, NICK!
ROLL PLAYBACK.
(ROCK MUSIC)
♪ PACK UP ♪
♪ I'M STRAIGHT ♪
♪ ENOUGH ♪
♪ OH SAY, SAY, SAY ♪
♪ WAIT, THEY DON'T LOVE YOU LIKE
I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ MAPS ♪
♪ WAIT, THEY DON'T LOVE YOU LIKE
I LOVE YOU ♪
(ROCK MUSIC)
♪ MADE OFF ♪
♪ DON'T STRAY ♪
♪ WELL, MY KIND'S YOUR KIND ♪
♪ I'LL STAY THE SAME ♪
♪ PACK UP ♪
♪ DON'T STRAY ♪
♪ OH SAY, SAY, SAY ♪
♪ WAIT, THEY DON'T LOVE YOU LIKE
I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ MAPS ♪
♪ WAIT, THEY DON'T LOVE YOU LIKE
I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ MAPS ♪
♪ WAIT, THEY DON'T LOVE YOU LIKE
I LOVE YOU ♪
(ROCK MUSIC)
♪ WAIT, THEY DON'T LOVE YOU LIKE
I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ MAPS ♪
♪ WAIT, THEY DON'T LOVE YOU LIKE
I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ MAPS ♪
♪ WAIT, THEY DON'T LOVE YOU LIKE
I LOVE YOU ♪
(ROCK MUSIC)